http://www.udans.com/pages/privacy-policy

Instagram
Free standard shipping over $75! *Expedited shipping unavailable due to COVID-19.
Free standard shipping over $75! *Expedited shipping unavailable due to COVID-19.
Events
Discover
About
Help Center
Upgrade your outdoor experience with the right apparel and footwear for conditions year-round.
Women's Apparel and Footwear
With functional and stylish gear, there's no compromise to look and feel great in any conditions.
Women's Footwear
Get the kiddos in gear all year round with apparel and footwear made to last.
Ski & Snowboard
Our Warehouse Sale - Online!
Shop the discounts we normally only offer in store at our annual warehouse sale
Privacy Policy
Uncle Dan's will not sell, share, trade or give away any personal information that it receives regarding its customers.
At udans.com, we are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect about you to process orders and to provide a more personalized shopping experience. Please read on for more details about our privacy policy.
What information do we collect? How do we use it?
This site is being monitored by one or more third-party monitoring software(s), and may capture information about your visit that will help us improve the quality of our service.
We collect the domain name of e-mail addresses of visitors to our site and aggregate (not personally identifiable) information on what pages visitors access. We use this information to monitor the use of the site and to improve its performance and usefulness. We also collect information you volunteer, such as survey responses, comments, purchasing and billing information, and your requests.
When you order, we need to know your name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit card number, phone number, and expiration date. This allows us to process and fulfill your order and to notify you of your order status.
We may also use the information we collect to occasionally notify you about important functionality changes to the Web site, new udans.com services, and special offers we think you'll find valuable.
How does udans.com protect customer information?
When you place orders or access your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. The secure server software (SSL) encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us. Furthermore, all of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access.
How does udans.com allow customers to update or change the information it collects?
You may update or change information related to your udans.com account by sending an email to support@gho.com
Yes, we do use cookies, but we do not overuse them!
Uncle Dan's, Rock/Creek, and Gearhead Outfitters use cookies to enhance your shopping and browsing experience. The text in a cookie, by itself, only tells us that you have visited our site before. It does not store any personal information such as your name, e-mail address, street address or phone number. Cookies are also used to maintain your shopping basket. All data contained in the shopping basket is kept on our server and not in the cookie your machine is assigned.
Links to other sites
Our site provides links to other sites and content on the Web. Uncle Dan's is not responsible for the privacy policies and content of those sites.
Your consent
By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of this information by udans.com. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
3rd Party Tracking
Uncle Dan's engages in third party services to provide analytics and advertisements on your behalf across the internet. These third party services may use cookies, IP addresses and other technologies to collect information about your use of services on our website so that we may determine page and content popularity and deliver content-relevant Remarketing Advertising targeted toward your interests. Access to your IP address does not allow access to your personal information. An IP Address stands for Internet Protocol Address, which is a unique identifier so specific data can be sent to a specific computer participating in a computer network, (browsing the internet). You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising using your Ads Preferences Manager.
Don't miss the adventure!
Sign up for email updates and exclusive offers:
stores!
Help Center
FAQs, order issues, returns questions, and more!We're here to help.
Buying Guides
Packing lists, product reviews, gear recommendations - get educated, and get outside!
Trustpilot
Cookie Policy: we use cookies to ensure you get the best experience on our website.
Got It!
